const AdverbQuestion = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following is an adverb of manner?",
        options: ["Quickly", " Yesterday ", "Five", "Beautiful"],
        correct_option: "Quickly"
      },
      {
        question: "Identify the adverb in the sentence:He speaks softly.?",
        options: ["Speaks", " Softly ", "He", "None of the above"],
        correct_option: "Softly"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose the correct adverb to complete the sentence: She sings ___.?",
        options: ["Tomorrow", " Happy ", "Loudly", "Table"],
        correct_option: "Loudly"
      },
      {
        question: "In the sentence They often visit the museum, what is the adverb?",
        options: ["They", " Often ", "Visit", "Museum"],
        correct_option: "Often"
      },
      {
        question: "Select the adverb from the options:?",
        options: ["Cloud", " Quickly ", "Tall", "Jump"],
        correct_option: "Quickly"
      },
      {
        question: "Identify the adverb in the sentence: He ran very fast.?",
        options: ["He", "Ran  ", "Very", "Fast"],
        correct_option: "Very"
      },
      {
        question: "Which word in the sentence is NOT an adverb: She cooks deliciously.?",
        options: [" She", "Cooks  ", "Deliciously", "None of the above"],
        correct_option: "Cook"
      },
      {
        question: "What type of adverb is used in the sentence: He arrived early?",
        options: ["Manner adverb", " Time adverb ", "Place adverb", "Degree adverb"],
        correct_option: "Time averb"
      },
      {
        question: "In the sentence She speaks quite softly. what is the adverb?",
        options: ["Speaks", " Quite ", "Softly", "She"],
        correct_option: "Quit"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose the correct adverb to complete the sentence:He reads ___.?",
        options: [" Book", " new", "Big", "Quickly"],
        correct_option: "Quickly"
      },

];
export default AdverbQuestion;